Welcome back to my series where I
recreate Ben & Jerry's flavors but lower
in calories and higher in protein. This
is tiramisu topped. Let me show you how
to make it. For the base, we're doing a
mascar pone flavored base. So, very
similar to my vanilla base, but we're
just adding in a little bit of mascar
pone. This makes it super thick and
creamy, which is exactly what we want,
if you know what I mean. Once you blend
that all together, you can throw it in
the freezer for at least 16 hours. Take
it out, run it under hot water for about
a minute and then throw it in your
creamy on the light ice cream setting.
Once that initial spin completes, you
can take it out and scrape down the
sides with a butter knife and then
hollow out a hole in the middle for your
mixins. Let's talk about the mix-ins.
So, for the shortbread component of the
Ben & Jerry's flavor, I'm using these
highkey wafers. This brand is awesome.
They make sugar-free and low calorie
versions of all your favorite treats.
And then for the chocolate coffee
component, I'm using chocolatecovered
espresso beans. These also give it a
nice crunch and I think they make the
perfect addition. And here's a mix-in
pro tip. Chop your mixins up into your
desired size and then freeze them for at
least an hour before using them. This
helps them stay intact and not get
obliterated by the mix-in setting. And
then all that's left to do is top it
with that sugar-free chocolate sauce.
And then one more chopped up espresso
bean.